Guide to the Yale Objects Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale objects collection, 1697-2002; Series I
  - #416 Piece of the first telegraph wire line [see Century Magazine, 1888 April], 1838 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - #417 Wooden spoon with blue ribbon; possibly a favor at a Wooden Spoon dance, undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - #418 Green bowl presented to: "Adolph B. Benson from the Royal New Sweden Tercentennary Commission with thanks.", 1938 (Box 99)
  - #419 Blue and red ribbon with medal attached. Awarded tor high jump, Yale-Harvard track athletic association, 1916 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - #420 Black ribbon with medal attached. Awarded for high jump, Intercollegiate Association of Amateur Athletes of Americirca, 1916 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - #421 Black ribbon with medal attached, awarded for high jump. Yale University, Spring Meet, 1915 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - #422 Black-Yellow-Blue ribbon with medal attached, awarded for high jump at Princeton-Yale track A.A, 1916 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - #423 Bronze medal commemorating 300th anniversary of New Haven, 1938 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - #424 Silver medal commemorating tercentenary of New Haven, 1938 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - #425 Small silver medal commemorating tercentenary of New Haven, 1938 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - #426 [Gold?] medal awarded to Yale Univ. (Ralph S. Hirshorn) for film "The End of Summer"--The Jesse L. Lasky Intercollegiate Film Award (c.f. YDN 1/28/60), 1960 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - #427 Bronze Medal inscribed "Freedom's Foundation at Valley Forge: For outstanding achievement in bringing about a better understanding of the American Way of.. ", 1957 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - #428 Bronze medal with frieze-like bust of Wm. Shakespeare. "To Yale Univ. For distinguished service to Shakespeare.", 1953-1954 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - #429 Sterling silver medal inscribed Yale University--Univ. of California, 1900 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - #430 An emblem in shape of a shield with an eagle on top, "spread-eagled." Inscription: "Presented to [Lynn Vern?] Esq. by the students of Yale College.", 1862 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - #431 Oval bronze medal struck for the 100th rowing of the "Yale--Harvard Regatta", 1965 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - #432 Oval bronze medal struck for the 100th rowing of the "Yale--Harvard Regatta", 1965 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - #433 Bronze medal struck in celebration of the Bicentennial of Yale University. Lux et Veritas, 1901 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - #434 Bronze medal struck in celebration of the Bicentennial of Yale University, 1901 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - #435 Bronze medal as a pin with blue ribbon struck in celebration of the Yale University Bicentennial, 1901 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - #436 Yale bicentennial medal. Lux et Veritas, 1901 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - #437 Yale bicentennial medal. Lux et Veritas, 1901 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - #438 Medal attached to blue ribbon with pin for class of 1883's 25th reunion, 1908 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - #439 Bronze medal as a pin with blue ribbon struck in celebration of the Yale University Bicentennial, 1901 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - #440 Class of 1892 medals with inscription, "New Haven: Fathers and sons of Yale." [2 medals welded into rectangular piece of metal], 45372 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - #441 Medal for Spring Games. 440 yard dash. Yale Athletic Association, 1892 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - #442 Boston Athletic Association [10kt] medal attached to green/gold ribbon, for the Invitation Games relay race, Harvard vs. Yale, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - #443 Track A.A. medal for Princeton-Yale mile run (with black-gold-blue ribbon), 1922 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - #444 10kt gold medal of University of Pennsylvania's 28th relay race Carnival, 3rd prize. Blue and maroon ribbon, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - #445 Silver Track Athletic Association medal for Harvard-Yale mile run, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - #446 Octagonal silver medal for Yale University Spring Meet. 1 mile run. Blue ribbon, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - #447 [Bronze] medal, Edward Livingston Trudeau Memorial. Awarded by the Nat'l Tuberculosis Assn. to Rudolph J. Anderson, Ph.D, undated (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - #448 Plastic cast of the Addison Emery Verrill Medal, awarded occasionally by the Peabody Museum, [1959]? (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - #449 Class of 1883 [bronze?] medal for 25th reunion. Blue ribbon, 1908 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - #450 Class of 1883 [bronze?] medal for 25th reunion. Blue ribbon, 1908 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - #451 Distinguished Flying Cross; awarded to Robert Lyman Rose, (Y. 1940) killed in action 1942. Red, white, and blue ribbon, 1943 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - #452 [Gold plated?] medal awarded to Dept. of Architecture of Yale by the Societe des architectes-gouvernement, 1924 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - #453 [Gold-plated?] medal awarded to Dept. of Architecture of Yale by the Societe des Architectes, 1933 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - #454 [Gold-plated?] medal awarded to Dept. of Architecture of Yale by the Societe des Architectes, 1937 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - #455 [Silver] Cobden Club Medal: "Free trade, peace, goodwill among nations." Awarded to Philip Ordway (see edge), undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - #456 [Gold-plated] New York Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, presented to Delano and Aldrich for distinguished work, 1921 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - #457 10 kt gold medal of the American Institute of Architects, presented to William A. Delano. 3 profiles, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - #458 14 kt. gold medal of the National Institute of Arts and Letters awarded to William A Delano, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - #459 [gold-plated?] medal of the National Institute of Social Sciences awarded to R.H. Chittenden, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - #460 Haskins medal of the Medieval Academy of America awarded to George Edward Woodbine, 1945 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - #461 Bronze. Theodore Dwight Woolsey medal (profile on front) celebrating his fiftieth anniversary, undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - #462 Bronze. Theodore Dwight Woolsey medal (profile on front) celebrating his fiftieth anniversary, undated (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - #463 Bronze. Theodore Dwight Woolsey medal (profile on front) celebrating his fiftieth anniversary, undated (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - #464 Silver medal: for service to Yale, undated (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - #465 Silver medal presented 1957 to Yale from Bahia University by the rector, Dr. E.R. Santos (Profiles of E. Gaspar Dutra, E.R. Santos and E. DeSouza Campos), 1946 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - #466 [Silver?] Civil War medal of George W. Arnold. Attached to medal is a shield with profile of McClellan, 1861 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - #467 Silver medal, Yale class of 1881 25th anniversary medal. Blue ribbon attached, circa 1906 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - #468 Croix de guerre. For service at Verdun, with shoulder regalia. Medal has red-green ribbon attached, 1914-1918 (Box 101, Folder 20-21)
  - #469 Yale class of 1896s. 35th year reunion medal. Blue and gold, circa 1931 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - #470 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1951 (Box 102A, Folder 1)
  - #471 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, undated (Box 102A, Folder 2)
  - #472 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1954 (Box 102A, Folder 3)
  - #473 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1949 (Box 102A, Folder 4)
  - #474 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1945 (Box 102A, Folder 5)
  - #475 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1943 (Box 102A, Folder 6)
  - #476 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold [key may never have been given to William Borden by Mr. Farr], 1942 (Box 102A, Folder 7)
  - #477 Phi Beta Kappa, gold, circa 1837 (Box 102A, Folder 8)
  - #478 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, circa 1931 (Box 102A, Folder 9)
  - #479 Hopkins Grammar School, gold, black, and white, Phi Sigma Tau, 1894 (Box 102A, Folder 10)
  - #480 gold, 1941s (Box 102A, Folder 11)
  - #481 Round; silver, blue, and white, 1896 (Box 102A, Folder 12)
  - #482 Psi Upsilon; gold and black triangle, undated (Box 102A, Folder 13)
  - #483 gold, white, and green stones; black, Alpha Delta Phi, 1871 (Box 102A, Folder 14)
  - #484 Gold Wolf's Head pin, 1873 (Box 102A, Folder 15)
  - #485 Delta Kappa; gold, black, and white crescent, 1873 (Box 102A, Folder 16)
  - #486 Delta Kappa Epsilon: triangle shape; gold, black, and white, 1873 (Box 102A, Folder 17)
  - #487 Round, silver, unusual design, 1873 (Box 102A, Folder 18)
  - #488 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; star-shaped, black and gold, 1866 (Box 102A, Folder 19)
  - #489 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1896 (Box 102A, Folder 20)
  - #490 gold and blue, 1910s (Box 102A, Folder 21)
  - #491 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1901 (Box 102A, Folder 22)
  - #492 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1898 (Box 102A, Folder 23)
  - #493 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1914 (Box 102A, Folder 24)
  - #494 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1917 (Box 102A, Folder 25)
  - #495 Kappa Alpha; gold, 1911 (Box 102A, Folder 26)
  - #496 Psi Upsilon; gold and black triangle, 1898 (Box 102A, Folder 27)
  - #497 Yale Pin; blue, gold, white; round; has seal, undated (Box 102A, Folder 28)
  - #498 Alpha Delta Phi; gold, white, black, and green, 1851 (Box 102A, Folder 29)
  - #499 Sigma Xi; gold, 1895s (Box 102A, Folder 30)
  - #500 Yale Dramatic Association, gold and blue, 1904 (Box 102A, Folder 31)
  - #501 Delta Beta Xi; gold, black, and white, undated (Box 102A, Folder 32)
  - #502 Chi Delta Theta, lit triangle, gold, 1824 (Box 102A, Folder 33)
  - #503 Phi Epsilon, gold, 1841 (Box 102A, Folder 34)
  - #504 Theta Kappa Alpha; blue and gold, 1873 (Box 102A, Folder 35)
  - #505 Gold inscription: NLD 1831 Natura (Box 102A, Folder 36)
  - #506 Sigma Xi; gold, 1895 (Box 102A, Folder 37)
  - #507 Class pin; gold, blue; clear stones, 1848 (Box 102A, Folder 38)
  - #508 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1870 (Box 102A, Folder 39)
  - #509 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1897 (Box 102A, Folder 40)
  - #510 Aurelian Society, gold, 1910 (Box 102A, Folder 41)
  - #511 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1902 (Box 102A, Folder 42)
  - #512 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1911 (Box 102A, Folder 43)
  - #513 Anchor shape, gold. "Swiss Marines" on front, 1917 (Box 102A, Folder 44)
  - #514 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1915 (Box 102A, Folder 45)
  - #515 Delta Phi pin; cross shape, gold and black, 1907 (Box 102A, Folder 46)
  - #516 Sigma Xi; gold, 1904 (Box 102A, Folder 47)
  - #517 Tau Delta Psi; gold and blue; T-shape, 1873 (Box 102B, Folder 48)
  - #518 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1929 (Box 102B, Folder 49)
  - #519 Sigma Delta Psi Athletic Honorary Society "Committee Key"; square; blue and gold, 1896 (Box 102B, Folder 50)
  - #520 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; black and gold; square, 1853 (Box 102B, Folder 51)
  - #521 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; star-shaped, black and gold, 1863 (Box 102B, Folder 52)
  - #522 Psi Upsilon; triangle shape, black and gold, 1882 (Box 102B, Folder 53)
  - #523 He Boule; black and gold; triangle shape, 1882 (Box 102B, Folder 54)
  - #524 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; anchor with serpent entwined; black and gold, 1882 (Box 102B, Folder 55)
  - #525 Phi Lamda Upsilon; gold, black, and white; hexagon shape, 1909 (Box 102B, Folder 56)
  - #526 Sigma Xi; gold, 1897 (Box 102B, Folder 57)
  - #527 Chi Delta Theta, gold triangle, 1831 (Box 102B, Folder 58)
  - #528 Chi Delta Theta, gold triangle, 1824 (Box 102B, Folder 59)
  - #529 Chi Delta Theta, gold triangle, "Yale Lit", 1836 (Box 102B, Folder 60)
  - #530 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold; black cloth attached, 1895 (Box 102B, Folder 61)
  - #531 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1896 (Box 102B, Folder 62)
  - #532 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1896 (Box 102B, Folder 63)
  - #533 Yale Banjo Club: gold, 1891 (Box 102B, Folder 64)
  - #534 Yale University Football Association gold football. "Yale 12 Harvard 0," and "Yale 12 Princeton 10.", 1907 (Box 102B, Folder 65)
  - #535 Yale pin; round; gold and white with blue stones and seal, 1914 (Box 102B, Folder 66)
  - #536 Yale Glee Club gold songbook charm, "S. Woodward" and "Yale Glee Club" on one side, ''Neath the Elms" on the other, 1884 (Box 102B, Folder 67)
  - #537 American Society of Civil Engineers; blue and gold shield, 1896 (Box 102B, Folder 68)
  - #538 Yale Daily News gold seal with blue ribbon and gold safety pin; "50th Anniversary 1878-1928" (Box 102B, Folder 69)
  - #539 Yale Record gold owl, undated (Box 102B, Folder 70)
  - #540 Brooch with man's head done in color, undated (Box 102B, Folder 71)
  - #541 Psi Gamma; gold and black triangle, 1885 (Box 102B, Folder 72)
  - #542 Psi Upsilon; gold and black triangle, 1896 (Box 102B, Folder 73)
  - #543 Psi Upsilon; gold and black triangle, 1842 (Box 102B, Folder 74)
  - #544 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1894 (Box 102B, Folder 75)
  - #545 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1892 (Box 102B, Folder 76)
  - #546 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1898 (Box 102B, Folder 77)
  - #547 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1880 (Box 102B, Folder 78)
  - #548 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold with pin, 1876 (Box 102B, Folder 79)
  - #549 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1890 (Box 102B, Folder 80)
  - #550 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1878 (Box 102B, Folder 81)
  - #551 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1879 (Box 102B, Folder 82)
  - #552 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1890 (Box 102B, Folder 83)
  - #553 Phi Gamma Delta; black, gold, and white diamond, 1864 (Box 102B, Folder 84)
  - #554 Chi Delta Theta, gold triangle, 1830 (Box 102B, Folder 85)
  - #555 Psi Gamma; gold and black diamond, 1885 (Box 102B, Folder 86)
  - #556 Psi Gamma; gold and black diamond, 1862 (Box 102C, Folder 87)
  - #557 Psi Gamma; gold and black diamond, 1887 (Box 102C, Folder 88)
  - #558 Chi Phi; gold; red, black, and white stones, 1879 (Box 102C, Folder 89)
  - #559 Psi Gamma; gold and black diamond, 1860 (Box 102C, Folder 90)
  - #560 Psi Gamma; gold and black diamond, 1893 (Box 102C, Folder 91)
  - #561 Calliopean Society Badge. Gold 5-pointed star, 1831 (Box 102C, Folder 92)
  - #562 Alpha Chi, gold and black, 1878 (Box 102C, Folder 93)
  - #563 25th Wedding Anniversary. Silver heart, undated (Box 102C, Folder 94)
  - #564 Yale Athletic Association, silver, undated (Box 102C, Folder 95)
  - #565 Gamma Delta Psi--Hillhouse High School. Black and gold crescent, 1894 (Box 102C, Folder 96)
  - #566 He Boule; black and gold diamond, 1882 (Box 102C, Folder 97)
  - #567 Mask and wig; blue, white, and gold, 1891 (Box 102C, Folder 98)
  - #568 American Association for the Advancement of Science; white plastic button, circa 1907 (Box 102C, Folder 99)
  - #569 American Association for the Advancement of Science; white plastic button with blue cloth, undated (Box 102C, Folder 100)
  - #570 American Association for the Advancement of Science; gold, red, blue, white, 1902 (Box 102C, Folder 101)
  - #571 American Association for the Advancement of Science; gold pin, 1902 (Box 102C, Folder 102)
  - #572 Yale Bicentennial Button--copper with purple ribbon, 1901 (Box 102C, Folder 103)
  - #573 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; black and gold, 1869 (Box 102C, Folder 104)
  - #574 Eta Sigma Tau; gold and black, 1899 (Box 102C, Folder 105)
  - #575 CRIKI; gold pen and scroll, 1899 (Box 102C, Folder 106)
  - #576 Alpha Delta Phi; gold, white, black, and green, 1866 (Box 102C, Folder 107)
  - #577 Alpha Delta Phi, gold crescent; star with green stone, 1859 (Box 102C, Folder 108)
  - #578 Alpha Delta Phi; gold white, black, green; white stones, 1864 (Box 102C, Folder 109)
  - #579 Alpha Delta Phi; gold and black; white stones; star and crescent, circa 1890's (Box 102C, Folder 110)
  - #580 Alpha Delta Phi; gold and black; star and crescent schape; green and white stones, 1890 (Box 102C, Folder 111)
  - #581 Alpha Delta Phi; gold, black, white, and green, 1841 (Box 102C, Folder 112)
  - #582 Theta Delta Chi; gold, black, and blue; white stones, 1895 (Box 102C, Folder 113)
  - #583 Alpha Sigma Phi; gold, black, white, 1856 (Box 102C, Folder 114)
  - #584 Chi Psi; gold with white stones, undated (Box 102C, Folder 115)
  - #585 Zeta Psi; gold with blue stones, 1903 (Box 102C, Folder 116)
  - #586 Delta Phi pin; cross shape, gold and black, 1899 (Box 102C, Folder 117)
  - #587 Delta Phi pin; cross shape, gold and black, 1899 (Box 102C, Folder 118)
  - #588 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; black and gold, 1882 (Box 102C, Folder 119)
  - #589 Delta Kappa; gold, black, and white crescent, 1873 (Box 102C, Folder 120)
  - #590 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; black and gold, 1856 (Box 102C, Folder 121)
  - #591 Gamma Nu; gold and blue, 1887 (Box 102D, Folder 122)
  - #592 He Boule; black, white, and gold diamond, 1893 (Box 102D, Folder 123)
  - #593 Sigma Delta; black, gold, and white diamond, 1899 (Box 102D, Folder 124)
  - #594 Gold Yale class key, 1836 (Box 102D, Folder 125)
  - #595 Vieta pin; black, gold, and white shield, 1859 (Box 102D, Folder 126)
  - #596 Yale pin; blue, white, and silver, 1897 (Box 102D, Folder 127)
  - #597 Alpha Sigma Phi; gold, black, white, 1866 (Box 102D, Folder 128)
  - #598 Chi Delta Theta, gold triangle, 1835 (Box 102D, Folder 129)
  - #599 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold with chain, 1896 (Box 102D, Folder 130)
  - #600 Delta Kappa Epsilon: triangle shape; gold, black, and white, 1878 (Box 102D, Folder 131)
  - #601 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1901 (Box 102D, Folder 132)
  - #602 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1869 (Box 102D, Folder 133)
  - #603 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1879 (Box 102D, Folder 134)
  - #604 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white, 1873 (Box 102D, Folder 135)
  - #605 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold with chain, 1889 (Box 102D, Folder 136)
  - #606 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1888 (Box 102D, Folder 137)
  - #607 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1886 (Box 102D, Folder 138)
  - #608 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1826 (Box 102D, Folder 139)
  - #609 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1831 (Box 102D, Folder 140)
  - #610 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1831 (Box 102D, Folder 141)
  - #611 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1837 (Box 102D, Folder 142)
  - #612 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1832 (Box 102D, Folder 143)
  - #613 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1840 (Box 102D, Folder 144)
  - #614 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1833 (Box 102D, Folder 145)
  - #615 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1835 (Box 102D, Folder 146)
  - #616 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1840 (Box 102D, Folder 147)
  - #617 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1846 (Box 102D, Folder 148)
  - #618 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1851 (Box 102D, Folder 149)
  - #619 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1863 (Box 102D, Folder 150)
  - #620 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1802 (Box 102D, Folder 151)
  - #621 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1865 (Box 102D, Folder 152)
  - #622 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1866 (Box 102D, Folder 153)
  - #623 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1871 (Box 102D, Folder 154)
  - #624 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1885 (Box 102D, Folder 155)
  - #625 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1882 (Box 102D, Folder 156)
  - #626 SSC Senior Council medal, gold, 1841 (Box 102D, Folder 157)
  - #627 SSC Senior Council, bronze, 1841 (Box 102D, Folder 158)
  - #628 Sigma Xi; gold, 1892 (Box 102D, Folder 159)
  - #629 Yale Courant, gold, 1896 (Box 103A, Folder 160)
  - #630 Eta Phi; gold, black and white diamond, 1892 (Box 103A, Folder 161)
  - #631 He Boule; black, white, and gold diamond, 1889 (Box 103A, Folder 162)
  - #632 Beta Chi; gold, black, and white crescent, 1887 (Box 103A, Folder 163)
  - #633 Delta Beta Xi; gold, black, and white, 1873 (Box 103A, Folder 164)
  - #634 Delta Beta Xi; gold, black, and white, 1869 (Box 103A, Folder 165)
  - #635 Delta Kappa; gold, black, and white crescent, 1872 (Box 103A, Folder 166)
  - #636 Kappa Psi; gold, black, and white diamond, 1912 (Box 103A, Folder 167)
  - #637 Chi Delta Theta; gold triangle, 1833 (Box 103A, Folder 168)
  - #638 Sigma Delta Psi; gold key, 1930 (Box 103A, Folder 169)
  - #639 Phi Theta Psi; gold, black, and white, 1870 (Box 103A, Folder 170)
  - #640 Alpha Delta Phi; black, gold, white, and green, 1857 (Box 103A, Folder 171)
  - #641 Alpha Sigma Phi; black, white, and gold. Also blue cloth with gold border "Yale", 1862 (Box 103A, Folder 172)
  - #642 Sigma Delta Psi; blue and gold key constitution also found. Given to PBS 1/28/83, 1902 (Box 103A, Folder 173)
  - #643 Sigma Xi; gold, 1894 (Box 103A, Folder 174)
  - #644 Kappa Psi; gold, black and white diamond, 1903 (Box 103A, Folder 175)
  - #645 Alpha Sigma Phi; black, white, and gold, 1865 (Box 103A, Folder 176)
  - #646 Delta Kappa; gold, black, and white crescent, 1875 (Box 103A, Folder 177)
  - #647 Sigma Xi; gold key, 1881 (Box 103A, Folder 178)
  - #648 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1819 (Box 103A, Folder 179)
  - #649 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1830 (Box 103A, Folder 180)
  - #650 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1874 (Box 103A, Folder 181)
  - #651 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1883 (Box 103A, Folder 182)
  - #652 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1883 (Box 103A, Folder 183)
  - #653 Class Day committee, Sheffield, gold, 1917 (Box 103A, Folder 184)
  - #654 Yale Championship Track Team, 1916 (Box 103A, Folder 185)
  - #655 Gold key, 1917 (Box 103A, Folder 186)
  - #656 Gold sunburst design, "A", 1917 (Box 103A, Folder 187)
  - #657 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold--from Columbia, 1887 (Box 103A, Folder 188)
  - #658 Kappa Sigma Epsilon; black and gold sunburst, 1865 (Box 103A, Folder 189)
  - #659 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1898 (Box 103A, Folder 190)
  - #660 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1873 (Box 103A, Folder 191)
  - #661 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1806 (Box 103A, Folder 192)
  - #662 Zeta Psi, gold charm, 1932 (Box 103B, Folder 193)
  - #663 Zeta Psi; gold with white stones, 1932 (Box 103B, Folder 194)
  - #664 Zeta Psi; gold with blue stones, 1932 (Box 103B, Folder 195)
  - #665 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1868 (Box 103B, Folder 196)
  - #666 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1845 (Box 103B, Folder 197)
  - #667 Key; Phi Beta Kappa, 1816 (Box 103B, Folder 198)
  - #668 Gold and glass pin, circa 1841 (Box 103B, Folder 199)
  - #669 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1855 (Box 103B, Folder 200)
  - #670 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1825 (Box 103B, Folder 201)
  - #671 Gold charm appearing to be some kind of crest. Elihu on back of box, 1891 (Box 103B, Folder 202)
  - #672 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold and black, 1867 (Box 103B, Folder 203)
  - #673 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1908 (Box 103B, Folder 204)
  - #674 Alpha Sigma Phi; black, white, and gold square, 1866 (Box 103B, Folder 205)
  - #675 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1857 (Box 103B, Folder 206)
  - #676 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1903 (Box 103B, Folder 207)
  - #677 Skull and Bones gold pin, circa 1902 (Box 103B, Folder 208)
  - #678 Skull and Bones gold key, circa 1902 (Box 103B, Folder 209)
  - #679 Skull and Bones gold key, undated (Box 103B, Folder 210)
  - #680 Class lapel buttons--gold and blue (2), 1885 (Box 103B, Folder 211)
  - #681 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1955 (Box 103B, Folder 212)
  - #682 Sigma Delta Chi; gold square, 1882 (Box 103B, Folder 213)
  - #683 Brothers in Unity; Silver Key, 1804 (Box 103B, Folder 214)
  - #684 The Yale Club of Chicago, plastic button with ribbon, blue and yellow, undated (Box 103B, Folder 215)
  - #685 Associated Western Yale Clubs lapel button with ribbon, blue and white, undated (Box 103B, Folder 216)
  - #686 Associated Western Yale Clubs, "Glad Hand Squad" lapel button with blue and white ribbons, 39215 (Box 103B, Folder 217)
  - #687 Yale lapel button with ribbon, blue and white, undated (Box 103B, Folder 218)
  - #688 Football reunion frame button with name, blue ribbon, 1905 (Box 103B, Folder 219)
  - #689 blue and white, "78", undated (Box 103B, Folder 220)
  - #690 Yale Reunion lapel button, blue "78", undated (Box 103C, Folder 221)
  - #691 Reunion button (lapel), blue "78", undated (Box 103C, Folder 222)
  - #692 Aurelian key; gold sunburst; "A", 1885 (Box 103C, Folder 223)